[
    {
        "Question": "True or False. No items should be kept above the Combi Oven.",
        "Answer": "TRUE (Verdadera)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What item does not go in corn salsa?",
        "Answer": "Black beans (Frijoles negros)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Steak markers should be placed in the steak.",
        "Answer": "FALSE (Falso)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Temperature danger zone is:",
        "Answer": "41°-135°"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Biotherm holder should contain ________ biotherms at all times.",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "For soups that require water to be added, ________ should be used.",
        "Answer": "Hot water from coffee machine / Agua caliente de la cafetera"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Salsa should be made on truck day.",
        "Answer": "True / Verdadero"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. You can use Chili's to-go boxes for IJW orders.",
        "Answer": "False / Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Ribs are basted with room temp BBQ sauce.",
        "Answer": "False/Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When making salsa, measure and pour _______ of water into each salsa pouch to rinse and pour on top of tomatoes.",
        "Answer": "1 cup / 1 taza"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the shelf life on Quesadilla presets?",
        "Answer": "28 hours (28 horas)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many total shakes are on a burger patty?",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "If a Guest orders a fajita trio with chicken, shrimp and beef, the beef should be plated in the __________ of the skillet.",
        "Answer": "Botom Right / Abajo a la derecha"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How often do you change out the Fry Bowl and pan?",
        "Answer": "Every 2 hours (Cada 2 horas)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the process in the event your Impinger goes down?",
        "Answer": "Use the impinger backup cooking procedures / Utilice los procedimientos de cocción de reserva del impinger"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Where do tortilla strips go when building a salad?",
        "Answer": "On the top (En la parte superior)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How often should the flat top be calibrated?",
        "Answer": "Twice a year / Dos veces al año"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How long is the shelf life on wings?",
        "Answer": "4 Days (4 días)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the internal cooking temperature of a RARE 6oz Sirloin?",
        "Answer": "125"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many times a day do we cut Avocado slices and where in the kitchen do you cut them?",
        "Answer": "Twice a day, in the prep area/ Dos veces al día, en el área de preparación"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the proper portion for FRIES on the side of an entrée?",
        "Answer": "6 oz."
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many shakes of salt total is used per lexan of chips?",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Once on the line, a ________ should be kept in the crisper batter.",
        "Answer": "4 oz. Ladle (Cucharón)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many orders of fries max can be cooked in one single fry basket?",
        "Answer": "5 orders/ 5 ordenes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are not served on a Quesadilla Explosion salad?",
        "Answer": "PICO"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False: The daily filter process should be completed on each fryer nightly.",
        "Answer": "TRUE (Verdadera)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Fajita beef should be cooked for how many mins per side?",
        "Answer": "2.5 mins // 2.5 minutos"
    },
    {
        "Question": "One 4-finger pinch of mushrooms gets ____ of garlic spread.",
        "Answer": "3 Lines"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When calibrating a thermometer place it in ice water and make sure it reads",
        "Answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When adding cooked pasta to Ice bath, how long should you stir?",
        "Answer": "5 minutes / 5 minutos"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. After cleaning all the parts of the Bun Toaster you should apply a small amount of salad oil to the rotating belt.",
        "Answer": "True/Verdadero"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How often do you boil out a fryer and how many at a time?",
        "Answer": "Once a week/One at a time Una vez a la semana/Una a la vez"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. The combi oven chamber must be cleaned at least once per day.",
        "Answer": "TRUE (Verdadera)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How long does Fajita beef need to air before it’s used on the line?",
        "Answer": "1 hour/ 1 hora"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many boneless wings in an order for PP Triple?",
        "Answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Citrus marinade is placed in a lined 1/6 pan?",
        "Answer": "TRUE (Verdadera)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "“Batch QTY” on a prep sheet means:",
        "Answer": "How many 1X recipe yields you need to make / Cuántos recetas 1X usted necesita hacer"
    },
    {
        "Question": "___________ is used for the Crisper Batter recipe.",
        "Answer": "Ice water / Agua helada"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. You should never leave Temperature Controlled for Safety (TCS) foods unattended at room temperature for more than 15 minutes.",
        "Answer": "False/ Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much alfredo sauce is on the Cajun pasta?",
        "Answer": "8 oz"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is on the bottom of the food hierarchy?",
        "Answer": "Raw Poultry / Aves crudas"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How often do you clean the burger smasher?",
        "Answer": "Every hour/ Cada hora"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Red onions do not need to be washed.",
        "Answer": "False/ Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many Crispers can you put in a vat of fry oil at a time?",
        "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How long do you re-crisp CRISPY CK?",
        "Answer": "30 seconds (30 segundos)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much water needs to be added when preparing BLK BEAN?",
        "Answer": "None (ninguno)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Reheated food for hot holding needs to reach what temperature?",
        "Answer": "165"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Kid chicken pasta is sold with?",
        "Answer": "Alfredo"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How should food be cooled?",
        "Answer": "A & B (Ice bath (Baño de hielo) & Sheet pan (Sartén))"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Steaks must be thawed:",
        "Answer": "For 24 hours in the walk-in / Durante 24 horas en el cuarto frío"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which kid's items come with CK SMALL?",
        "Answer": "All of the Above (Todas las anteriores)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many swirls of ranch on each QUESA TORT?",
        "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many total lines of sauce should you use to coat an order of 12 wings?",
        "Answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Yellow Zone indicates which prep area?",
        "Answer": "Raw Poultry (Aves crudas)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When cleaning slicer, dicers, and wedgers you should lubricate all ___________ with Petro Gel.",
        "Answer": "Sliding Pieces/ Piezas deslizantes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Proper cooling gets product to _______ degrees as quickly as possible.",
        "Answer": "41"
    },
    {
        "Question": "One avocado will yield how many slices?",
        "Answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. FRIES are placed on the basket by FOH TMs.",
        "Answer": "True/Verdadero"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. CRISPY CK is ladled with WINGSAUCE on the RANCHSAND.",
        "Answer": "FALSE (Falso)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Salad oil can be used to lubricate the Rotary Slicer as needed.",
        "Answer": "False/Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When should steaks be temped with a biotherm?",
        "Answer": "Every steak should be temped prior to selling / A cada filete se le debe medir la temperatura antes de venderlo"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Bone in wings are recrisped?",
        "Answer": "True / Verdadero"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does FIFO mean?",
        "Answer": "First in first out / Primero en entrar, primero en salir"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many cooked skillet cookies fit into each container?",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. For Ribs, Pull-thaw is a 48-hour process.",
        "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Regardless of the items you have on the line, you should always pull ALL the items on your Pull Thaw sheet.",
        "Answer": "FALSE (Falso)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Thawing frozen chicken at room temperature is acceptable.",
        "Answer": "False/ Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When smoking ribs, the combi must be:",
        "Answer": "Heated (Calentado)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many snake shakes of char seasoning for a 1x batch of Fajita Onions on the Flattop?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What should you do if a pan catches fire inside the CTX?",
        "Answer": "Push it through and smother it with a sheet tray / Empujarlo y sofocarlo con una plancha para hornear"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When prepping Fajita Onions on the flattop (non KOF III), what is the total cook time?",
        "Answer": "8 min"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many shakes of margarita seasoning is on the Margarita Chicken",
        "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When should Cheese be placed on the burger?",
        "Answer": "On the flip (en la tapa)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "All IJW orders come with 2 sides of Ranch.",
        "Answer": "FALSE (Falso)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the internal cooking temperature of fajita beef?",
        "Answer": "158"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Foods cannot safely remain in the TDZ for more than?",
        "Answer": "4 hours/ 4 horas"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the standard hold time for Chicken in the ACT bins?",
        "Answer": "30 min"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How long is rice good for being held in the hot well?",
        "Answer": "4 hours/ 4 horas"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many cuts per stalk of green onion?",
        "Answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Guacamole nearing the end of its shelf-life can be used to make Avocado Ranch.",
        "Answer": "True/Verdadero"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Minimum cooking temperatures must be held for ______ seconds in order to be considered safe.",
        "Answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following should be used to clean the surface of the Flat Top Grill?",
        "Answer": "Salad oil/ Aceite para ensaladas"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. The Crisper Breading Procedure should only be used during peak hours.",
        "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Minimum internal cooking temperature of kid burger bites?",
        "Answer": "180"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When prepping Salad mix, what should you do with the lettuce?",
        "Answer": "Break up any large pieces (Rompe cualquier pieza grande)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What side of the grill pans need to be re-seasoned?",
        "Answer": "Both sides/ Ambos lados"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How long do you blend citrus marinade?",
        "Answer": "3 minutes (3 minutos)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many shakes of season salt is needed for 1/2 bag of fries?",
        "Answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. All skillets should be on a pan before running through the impinger.",
        "Answer": "True/Verdadero"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Your kitchen labeler (KitchenSYNC or Ithaca) should be cleaned every time you load a new roll to remove any adhesive residue. What should you use to clean it?",
        "Answer": "Sanitizer towel / Toalla desinfectante"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Fries older than ___ mins cannot be sold to Guests.",
        "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much MIX C is on a fajita boat?",
        "Answer": "4 Finger Pinch (1/2 cup)/ Una pizca de 4 dedos (1/2 taza)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many QUESAWDG come with the PPEXPLOSAL?",
        "Answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Phase butter should not be heated before adding to the bun toaster.",
        "Answer": "False/Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Ribs are thawed:",
        "Answer": "In the walk in, on sheet trays (En la entrada, en bandejas de hojas.)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much butter oil goes on the Avo Sirloin?",
        "Answer": "none/nada"
    },
    {
        "Question": "After cleaning a cooking surface with a cleaning solution (or any place food may come in contact with the equipment) you should wipe over the surface with _________________.",
        "Answer": "A sanitizer towel/ Una toalla desinfectante"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Pan release spray should be kept away from high heat always.",
        "Answer": "True/Verdadero"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which CTX pans are one time use only?",
        "Answer": "Seafood pans (Sartenes de marisco)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "True or False. Seasoned shrimp is portioned into bags of 6.",
        "Answer": "False/Falso"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many Crispers go on a CC SANTA SAL?",
        "Answer": "2"
    }
]
